const questionsObj = [
        {
            question: 'Considered mans bestfriend',
            answer: 'dog',
            level: 1,
        },
        {
            question: 'These animals fly, build nests and lay eggs',
            answer: 'bird',
            level: 1,
        },
        {
            question: 'Domesticated felines that cause chaos in peoples homes',
            answer: 'cat',
            level: 1,
        },
        {
            question: 'The king of the jungle',
            answer: 'lion',
            level: 1,
        },
    {
        question: 'A game console the preceded the nintendo 64',
        answer: 'super nintendo',
        level: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'The most popular game franchise on the original Xbox',
        answer: 'halo',
        level: 2,
    },
    {
        question: 'Battle Royale style game that became popular in 2018',
        answer: 'fortnite',
        level: 2,
    },
    {
        question: 'Sonys original handheld gaming console',
        answer: 'psp',
        level: 2,
    },
    {
        question: 'The original creator of Disneyland',
        answer: 'walt disney',
        level: 3,
    },
    {
        question: 'The yellow pup who lives with Mickey and Minnie',
        answer: 'pluto',
        level: 3,
    },
    {
        question: 'The original Angry Duck',
        answer: 'donald duck',
        level: 3,
    },
    {
        question: 'Rollercoaster type ride at disney\'s Tomorrowloand',
        answer: 'space mountain',
        level: 3,
    },
    {
        question: 'Hondas most popular model',
        answer: 'civic',
        level: 4,
    },
    {
        question: 'The first all electric production car',
        answer: 'roadster',
        level: 4,
    },
    {
        question: 'Car model offten referred to as the "Pony Car"',
        answer: 'mustang',
        level: 4,
    },
    {
        question: 'Itialian sports car with a horse as its logo',
        answer: 'ferrari',
        level: 4,
    },
    {
        question: 'The brain of a PC',
        answer: 'cpu',
        level: 5,
    },
    {
        question: 'Acronym for Random Access Memory',
        answer: 'ram',
        level: 5
    },
    {
        question: 'The main graphics processor of a PC',
        answer: 'gpu',
        level: 5,
    },
    {
        question: 'main circuit board in a pc',
        answer: 'motherboard',
        level: 5,
    },
];

// const levelTwoQuestions = [
//     {
//         question: 'A game console the presedesd the nintendo 64',
//         answer: 'super nintendo',
//         level: 2
//     },
//     {
//         question: 'The most popular game on the original Xbox',
//         answer: 'halo',
//         level: 2,
//     },
//     {
//         question: 'Battle Royale style game that became popular in 2018',
//         answer: 'fortnite',
//         level: 2,
//     },
//     {
//         question: 'Sonys original handheld gaming console',
//         answer: 'psp',
//         level: 2,
//     }
// ]

// const levelOneQuestions = {
//     1: [
//         {
//             question: 'Considered mans bestfriend',
//             answer: 'dog',
//             level: 1,
//         },
//         {
//             question: 'These animals fly, build nests and lay eggs',
//             answer: 'bird',
//             level: 1,
//         },
//         {
//             question: 'Domesticated felines that cause chaos',
//             answer: 'cat',
//             level: 1,
//         },
//         {
//             question: 'The king of the jungle',
//             answer: 'lion',
//             level: 1,
//         },
//     ],
//     2: [
//     {
//         question: 'A game console the presedesd the nintendo 64',
//         answer: 'super nintendo',
//         level: 2
//     },
//     {
//         question: 'The most popular game on the original Xbox',
//         answer: 'halo',
//         level: 2,
//     },
//     {
//         question: 'Battle Royale style game that became popular in 2018',
//         answer: 'fortnite',
//         level: 2,
//     },
//     {
//         question: 'Sonys original handheld gaming console',
//         answer: 'psp',
//         level: 2,
//     }
// ]
// };

export { questionsObj };

